[Music]
welcome um who she in herself is a live
streamer she's um she's the owner of
wine Antics so anyone that likes all the
ladies out there all the fellas that
like wine you definitely want to I put
the link up in my description you want
to click that link and then she's
launching a summit ladies go live she
has a um uh I'll let her explain um more
about ladies go live but I've been
watching what they've been doing in the
live streaming uh realm of things and
and it it's it's amazing to see people
come together sharing wonderful ideas so
I want you guys to give a round a
virtual Round of Applause for Miss Jen
Nelson yay I'll give myself a virtual
round the tradition
is we want to um we want to ask you what
your story is because you know the our
slogan is is that we expand the
crop and we we want to know like
everyone puts they everyone has an ego
they put themselves out there because
they they have a Brands to protect Etc
but we want to know a little bit more
about you and we want to know how you
how you even became an entrepreneur so
you know tell us your
story uh I hated working in a
cubicle I mean it's just it's that
simple is that I I had a a job and I
hated working in a cubicle and I wanted
to get away from it I wanted to and best
way I knew how to do that was to go out
on my own I have I had uh I I come from
a military background and I had quite a
number of years spend overseas so I
saved up my money and knew that from a
very young age this is what I wanted to
do I wanted to try something of my own
create something of my own uh in instead
of building other people's dreams I
think that's kind of how many
entrepreneurs start and I hope that you
can still hear me Ryan yeah I can still
hear you can you oh
good yeah um I think that's how many
people
are because you need to have that
underlying like burning desire to be
independent and be your own person and
have that Creative Energy cuz resilience
is a beast when it comes to
making making it year after year and I I
know I'm preaching to the choir when I
talk to you about it honestly it was
just I didn't want to work in a cubicle
I didn't want to build anybody else's
dreams I thought I would go into this is
definitely as the the wine aspect right
um it's been a little bit harder to run
that route um and I also love technology
and I love live streaming so I've been
trying to Teeter both the best that I
can mhm did you always know that you you
wanted to be a
entrepreneur um I think I think yes
because there's a funny story that came
up like I knew I wanted to be an
entreprene entrepreneur when I was a kid
and somebody would give the example uh
mine was I was I was bought these little
kits um and they were little glass or
plastic uh uh suncatchers so you could
paint them and they would look like
stained glass and um I did a bunch of
them I bought like two or three kids and
then I went around to my neighborhood
when I was probably in fifth fifth grade
and tried to sell them door too I also
had that very traditional lemonade stand
right uh when I was a kid and that stuff
must have been horrible if I can
remember it but like I I don't know I
mean our time growing up was so
different than what it is now I mean
fifth graders that are entrepreneurs
nowadays are running digital agencies
right right uh no my day it was a
lemonade stand and trying to sell Sun
Catchers door
too wow wow and like did you like was
that your idea did your parents
encourage you um how you know what what
would cuz some kids don't want to you
know sell things door too some kids
wanted to go play bikes or they wanted
to Rough House or or what what have you
but you know in your case like what made
you want to to to
sell I I I don't remember that far back
but my mother has always been the one
who has tried to start llc's and she's
been interested in teaching the
fundamentals of of What It Is to Be Your
Own Boss and understand uh what it takes
to start your own business and uh you
know a little bit of romanticizing the
notion of Entrepreneurship for me so
when you grow up in an environment where
it it is a romantic notion that's
actually a good thing because if if my
mom were to have been like a really
super successful entrepreneur it would
have given me some Headway you know I
would have been more like Gary Vee and
having a business set up for me uh but
if if it would have struggled and she
would have failed maybe I wouldn't have
tried but because she kept trying and
she a little bit romanticized it and put
it as a fantasy because she always
wanted to do it but never did it made it
seem like a very attainable and very
desirable thing for me from a very young
age mhm now uh moving into
adulthood you went into the military yes
and you
know that I mean like it just takes a
lot of guts just to to even think that
you want to go into the military cuz I
mean you know there's uh like I've had
friends that were in the military that
um that have seen a lot you know and
it's the unfortunate part but the great
thing is that you're serving your
community so what does what um
what propelled you to Surf your
community you know I would love to say
that I had the the flag waving in the
background and I was thinking of bald
eagles and all of these American
patriotic things in my mind no uh Jen
didn't want to pay for
college
um I it's like when it comes down to
like all these things that I may or may
not have um accomplished in life it's
just because I don't want to do
something that's that is going to cost
me too much money or is going to be
super difficult or a solution for why I
for what I don't know what I want to do
the military was a combination of me not
wanting to pay for college so get the
military to pay for college and I didn't
want to waste money in trying to go to
college and decide what I wanted to do
when I had no bloody idea what I wanted
to go to college for so it just seemed
like a giant waste of money that my
mother would have given me she would
have given me every opportunity and I
would have worked my butt off for it but
I didn't know like I didn't even know
where to start so it's like why not
stall a little bit and go in the
military it was a very different time
when I joined the military uh I signed
up at 17 back in 1999 and yes I'm I'm
dating myself now um and this was before
911 so it was a different um peacetime
military for the Army and it was a lot
of the mentality of serve your time
right uh and come out ahead of the game
you know come out at
2122 having some World Experience gone
around around the world a little bit met
different cultures had a chance to
travel and you have money set aside for
college when you want to get when you
get out that's awesome now um would you
ever if you ever had the opportunity
would you would you well let's say let's
say you went back in time and you were
given that decision to go to the Mia
would you would you have gone the same
direction
absolutely absolutely like there is not
a moment of hesitation um even though
I've served in I served one tour in Iraq
uh for the military and then a couple
for my federal service time uh probably
about redoing like what I do anything
over again uh by joining the military as
I as I said no and I I'm actually one of
the few people probably now because I'm
older and I can say this but I believe
that some kind of civil service should
be a requirement from anybody coming out
of college and Civil Service doesn't
mean uh military it can mean you know
being a fireman being EMT being a police
officer maybe being even being a nurse
or something in the medical profession
or social services right those are civil
services those are supporting Society
for two years and Korea does this I
spent some time in South Korea they have
a mandatory I think two or threee
service for all men and I don't believe
it needs to be all men I think it needs
to be women and men in America um and
and that is an opportunity for you to
want and save money you know get a
little bit of support and a little bit
of help get some job skills and just
think think and breathe out of high
school right right right right now from
the military when you got out what did
you do like what what happened
next I so I got out I was actually in
the initial invasion in Iraq so I got
stop held stop loss stop movement stop
everything my life was put on hold
because of the Iraq War and uh I got
back like within a month from my ETS so
that's the your final date of departure
and you're supposed to go through like
six months of transition like all this
uh career educational um you know
getting your benefits taken care of no I
got a month I had just come back from
Iraq and I had a month to take leave and
to leave the Army wow and no options for
anybody because literally everybody was
just coming back from irq so there were
zero options for me there wasn't you
know a sign on bonus there wasn't
another Duty station in line it was just
oh oh did you want to reinlist right now
okay you can stay at Fort Stewart uh
which is in Georgia a little bit uh
south of Savannah uh you could stay here
and be guaranteed another three
deployments to the s box I.E Iraq uh or
you can get out and here's your here's
your papers kind of deal so I got
out uh I went home uh for about a month
and uh found out I couldn't I couldn't
do it I could I couldn't be that person
again I couldn't my mother you know
welcomed me back in I have a great St
stable family life but it was like you
had been an adult for four years and
you'd been to a combat zone you've been
to basic training and you'd done all
these things and it's just like yeah I'm
I can't I need to be by myself so I
packed up my Mustang at the time and I
moved to DC and within two months I had
a job as a federal contractor and then
moved over to Federal
service what is a federal contractor or
what what do you do there a federal
contractor is just somebody that works
for the federal government uh they're
the bigger uh very expensive companies
around the DC area like Booze Allen
Hamilton uh Bae like MCH really big
northr Grumman is a federal contractor
so uh I worked with one of them for
about a month and then I picked up
another job working with the Department
of Defense wow that's amazing so then
what decided what what prompted you to
quit and to kind of get onto this cuz I
like was there another thing that
transitioned after that or did you kind
of transition and doing yourself you
know becoming a self-employed you know
live streamer and and wine Antics antic
I have no idea how I got here
today don't know um and I think I I
think that's pretty actually fair to say
as an entrepreneur is like you if you
find Opportunities and you jump on those
opportunities it's going to it's going
to propel you down a path you may not
have planned for but you're very happy
to ride with right um I there was a time
like in 2007 I really started to dislike
the way it was to be not to be a federal
employee but the the whole job space the
the um the roles that I had done within
in the government I just didn't want to
do it anymore I didn't want to work in a
cubicle maze um I wanted something
different I didn't think that my job was
actually relevant honestly outside of
those four walls and that's what kind of
happens in federal surface you get kind
of typ cast you're not flexible you're
not able to move around and this is this
is our generation right our generation
uh wants to be able to do different
things every three years or try
different things be creative think
outside the there was none of that okay
there was none of that um so I started
preparing in 2007 and then I think it
was like 2013 2014 i' kind of reached a
crossroad where I had to start pushing
for management or I needed to find
another way out and I decided that I had
enough things saved up uh I had done
enough studying I checked on my
retirement literally went down to HR
checked on my retirement to see how much
I would have for my 10 years of federal
service and laughed laughed at what I
could what I had and laughed at what I
could what was projected at the 20 year
and 30-y year mark and I'm like I am not
no have a nice day he literally laughed
hr's
face I was like okay thanks
start a second
career that's that's an amazing story so
now you're here so what is with you and
your fixation with
wine Oh you mean how did I get bit by
the wine bug
yes so uh when I was working in
Arlington um there is a a place called
the Washington wine Academy that
actually doesn't exist anymore and it's
very sad but I randomly found a deal for
some wine certification classes and I
was like what do I really care about I'm
sitting here again in a cubicle maze
with no windows no you know no happiness
all around me cuz when you work in the
Department of Defense you are working in
in the mentality of defense and none of
that is really positive if you start to
really think about what defense means
right and so I was like I just want a
profession that people are happy to see
me that's it like that's where it
started like where would I be happy and
where would people be happy to see me uh
and I went circles and circles and
circles for weeks about what I would
what I really wanted to do and what
would make me happy and it kept goinging
going back to wine and I had started
doing some wine festivals where I
volunteered and this was on totally on
my free time and just kind of
experienced the culture and the way
people react to you when you're pouring
wine or serving wine or drinking wine
like people are happy MH freaking happy
i' never experienced this before true
story people are actually happy and they
want to see me and they're happy to see
me and they look at me like I because I
care right I care to study and I care to
learn they look at me like I actually
know what I'm talking about versus what
I had done in in my current job there
was always somebody trying to sharpshoot
me right and that's just the the nature
of that environment so it was it's a
change of culture it was a change of um
what I mentally wanted to do creativity
being outside actually working in
agriculture um CH like that's another
component for wine for me it's not they
are small families it's Agriculture and
then it's a lot of fun to be in so I
went and took one of the certification
classes from the Washington wine Academy
and I never looked back wow I think
that's amazing I I I think your story is
it's different because you normally hear
it's either someone had a lot of
problems and then they became an
entrepreneur or someone was you know
brought into money through their parents
and then they started ideas but you know
your your story is really interesting um
when you started doing wine
Antics what were your challenges that um
that you had starting up because we all
have our startup challenges like what
were yours I don't actually I'm I'm a
wine blogger that doesn't like to
blog okay and that's that's an ongoing
challenge you know because I I didn't
start I think I wrote like two blogs
before I was like yeah this is not for
me this is not what I want to do and
luckily digital marketing was really
picking up I spent a lot of time on
social media just kind of engaging and
and talking to people and meeting people
in the wine community so I didn't really
do any like pure content and then live
streaming came along and I started doing
live streaming on Periscope back in
November of
2015 and um um I think one of my biggest
challenges and the constant challenge
that it is is what's the value of live
streaming like in the tech space it's a
little bit easier nowadays in the
marketing space it's becoming easier the
wine industry barely recognizes
podcasting and
vlogging so so you know as a legitimate
form of content creation right um so
coming at it from a live stream
perspective like people are like you you
do what
oh that's like vlogging right no sweetie
no sweetie that's not like
vlogging oh it's like podcast no sweetie
like so I you know I even ran into
somebody today that was like oh I like
your name because wine Antics is funny
it gives me permission to not only talk
about wine but beer and Spirits as well
which if you're a wine lover normally
you need a break from wine and you want
to try other things um so I wanted to
develop that that name intentionally and
they messaged me on Twitter and they
were like oh I'd love you to be a guest
feature or a guest or do a guest post on
my blog I'm like sure I'd love to let me
know how I can live stream for that
because I'm not I don't technically blog
but I live stream and for the first time
somebody actually came back to me and
like yeah what's that let's let's see
how we can make that work so hopefully
knock on wood it's changing yeah yeah
for sure now you've um you you
you you are now a producer with vit mug
and you met jonthan trip how did you two
meet blab like where everybody seems
like meet
right um blab was this amazing remote
island right where all live streamers
came to like see what can we do what can
we do that isn't Periscope or mircat at
that time or Google Hangouts blab was
this amazing Island where we could get
creative and start to think about it and
apparently build this amazing Community
but yeah I met him on blab just like
almost
everybody wow and so what was it about
him uh that made you think hey I should
partner with him and create a production
company because a production company is
as we can all
tell no joke right it's no joke yeah
it's no joke yeah um so you always want
to look at when you're looking for
mentors and I know you've talked about
this in the past when you're looking for
mentors or you're looking for business
partners and this is this is real raw
and real honest here you always want to
you want to look at somebody or partner
with somebody that's doing something
that you either admire that you can't do
or is at a higher a little bit of a
higher level than what you're doing and
I always looked at what Jonathan did as
I was playing like catchup to him like I
was I was trying to take what he was
doing and rip it to its fundamentals and
seeing how I can make it work for for me
and I know you do this behind the scenes
too and it's what everybody should be
doing if there's something that somebody
is doing don't completely imitate what
they're doing but try to make it work
for you because if it's working for them
it can work for you and this is how you
grow and develop so I don't think
Jonathan even knows this and why I chose
him but um it's because he was good he
was good at what he did and I felt like
he could make me better and I wanted to
live up to his expectations and I wanted
to provide a solid
partnership wow you know I and I that's
what I I really respect about you is
that um you're really humble you know oh
am I
yeah you're humble you're humble uh
because I think that uh for all the work
that you've done you do great work but
you know you you you have a great way of
acknowledging people and really
recognizing the great qualities of of
the people around you you know and
that's what makes a great um not only a
great leader um but it just makes a
great business person you know to to be
able to know the great people in the
room to be able to Source them out and
to work you know or if they sourced you
out either way it's like this Collective
of people coming together because they
acknowledge each other's strengths
because it's the people that are jealous
and you know um think that they can do
it all themselves that that are the ones
that f
but yet you know you and Jonathan put
together such a great uh surface that
you know it's we going to look back
because I always say like we're at the
we're at the edge of the wave here like
we are like the Philip def franos of
this I I say it you know like we are the
Philip def franos of this Avenue because
you know this is something we all jumped
on because we needed a place to stay you
know we needed blab kicked us out but
yeah but you're you're doing so well
with um with the teams that you that you
have there and even the ladies go live
now I want to talk about that oh thank
you good I want to talk about that too
on my mind it's in my notebook like most
of my stuff to-do list is all ladies go
live stuff because that's happening on
Friday so tell us about ladies go live
that was a great saguar H so um tell us
about ladies go live and and why you're
so um busy these last couple holay doing
all this stuff like what's going on so
uh I'll back it up to when I left my
full-time employment um I I did spend a
lot of time evaluating what I wanted to
to put back into the universe what I
wanted to put back into being an
entrepreneur and my work outside of my
previous job and I broke it down to four
things I I what I care about right um
I've learned over time that I've cared I
care about live streaming and digital
marketing in a broader sense I care
about tech I like technology I feed off
of it I like learning about it reading
about it and seeing different ways that
people are using it and can use it for
different ways uh I'm a veteran and I
care a lot about being a veteran and
Veterans rights because that's my future
let's be real right that's my future um
and then women's issues because I've
been through some stuff in my life and I
think every woman has a story to tell if
you have a perfect clean squeaky record
you didn't live right and I think that
goes for both women and men um so in
those four things I have fulfilled you
know you know at least two of them right
um a veteran is a the veteran thing is a
very slow yet steady steady Force like
support veterans um do the best that you
can to um recognize what people are
doing in the community try to support
those that are doing it right stand up
for your rights and make sure you know
in a political space that you have what
you uh what is fair I don't want to say
what you deserve but what is fair and
then I haven't done anything for women
really so when ladies go live came up it
was an opportunity for for me to fulfill
that fourth thing that I wanted to what
I want to do outside of my previous job
and uh zeep xan was the one who brought
me in and it's been a roller coaster I'm
not even going to lie I don't know how
many big teams you've worked on but
working with four different
personalities is is no small all feet
especially for something that was kind
of kind of from birth to actual
like like for no from conception to
birth which will be on Friday because
we're going with your analogy of giving
birth to the the hustle Zone TV um uh it
it's been a very condensed time it's
been probably about four or five months
to put the whole thing together and uh I
just like the fact that the Perry girls
is a great example of how a women's
Community can really boost each other
and move forward and help each other and
I think that there's still a space for
different women uh who aren't just you
know maybe maybe not just Periscope
related or maybe not just Liv streaming
related but maybe digital marketing or
even in the live streaming space there
may be some room for it but uh there's
there's a niche for everything and and
this one is just really working out for
like I said one of my for things that I
really care about that's amazing so how
are we um how can they find this Summit
that coming up here oh it's super easy
right ladies go.com thank you for that
reminding me why thank you for that
reminder Ryan ladies go.com you you
register on eventbr you treat it just
like a regular conference even though
this is a virtual conference 100%
virtual happening in two two Facebook
groups so all of the content will be
there so you go register at ladies.com
sign up on Eventbrite keep that code and
then you gain access to these two groups
and we'll be streaming all day long and
then uh it'll be up for 24 hours after
the content has aired and then it goes
down and you know what happens after
that right it's only free for so much
time yeah that's right that's right wow
that's that's a great idea like I think
uh you know we're we're we're really
making use of this virtual space that we
have um and doing some creative uh
events and I and I I recommend everyone
uh to follow Jen and follow wine Antics
follow ladies go live make sure you guys
sign up um via event brigh uh to to H
ladies go live Summit uh that's
happening on Friday so um I have to um
so we got part two of the the interview
questions before we are done well
there's a part two yes there I made it
so far I did so well so um first
question is what's your favorite
dessert anything chocolate dessert is
not dessert unless it has
chocolate like that's real easy for me I
don't want no pie I don't want no sorbet
I don't want I don't want a tart unless
it's got chocolate in it what's your uh
Michael Jackson or Prince
honestly
neither what would you what like in in
that case what what do you listen to
what kind of music do you listen to I
was gonna say I like music better so
Prince but um what kind of music do I
listen to so it's mix of actually
classical while I'm working and then
it's like techno and pop when I'm
working out and Country when I want to
chill and drink like it's all mood
dependent okay now favorite television
show guilty pleasure or like legit
watching legit watching Game of Thrones
Game of Thrones and I I haven't seen the
show and I don't get why people like it
so much you this is you got to get
through get through the first season and
you will understand it's it's like
everything else it's like it's drama
it's um a soap opera it's history it's
period pieces it's really great acting
like it's it's a nice package awesome
what's your favorite
movie
um uh Beauty and the Beast honestly
Beauty and the Beast yeah it's still one
of my favorite movies like the original
one the original Disney I could watch
that over and over again nice now um if
you could be in a movie which movie
would you be in oh you know who had can
I be the actress yes you could be the
actress I would I would want to be
Charlie theen in um uhan flux or what's
her name um Malo uh what's her name the
one in the Fifth
Element Mina is it Mera I don't even
remember a somebody tell me in the
comments
mirich yeah or Resident Evil like all
these strong women that are
badasses and they're not like like maybe
in the Fifth Element she was a little
bit more of a sex symbol but like just
really strong women roles right yeah um
with with that being said you like I
mean you are a strong woman right and
the fact that you like you serve for
your country you know you're the true
hero like I don't think I think people
should be playing you instead of the
other way around don't you think I don't
I
I I have been in a lot of situations
where people have given me that
compliment and I think you know most um
veterans will treat it one or two ways
they'll they'll acknowledge it and say
thank you right or they will totally
blow it off like because it's just it's
not a matter of of doing it or not doing
it's a matter of just doing what you
have to do and not thinking about
anything else and that's the you know
that fight or flight thing well well
it's a lot of fighting and you just have
that automatically programmed in right
right right so uh what makes you angry
Jen
oh
uh I don't you know what really makes me
angry there
is a lot of things honestly that make me
angry and I try to let a lot of things
go but like if you got drama and if you
got beef don't put it in public if you
you don't come to my like I sound like
I'm from the hood all of a sudden but
like but like don't have beef don't
bring drama unless you're going to
unless you're going to talk to me like
this is adult 101 right communication
and if you're going to if you have
something to say if you're not able to
say it to my face there's no validity in
in public
spaces yeah I have to agree with that
statement now what makes you sad like
what makes you cry literally everything
on TV I don't
know like what was I watching I was
watching Leah reminy uh on her
Scientology special and I don't know if
you've caught that but it's very moving
um there is some
very strange principles with Scientology
Y and hearing the Survivor Stories the
people that have left Scientology and
are brave enough to talk about what is
going on like I watched that today and I
was Balling on my couch
talking about people reacting to Suicide
like people in ch in the church feeling
so distraught with their experiences
that they've committed suicide and then
hearing the Survivor stories like
literally everything on TV I'm sure Game
of Thrones is made me cry at
some yeah well but you know like that's
another live stream you know just the
that that document or not the docu is it
a doc series or is a documentary no it's
all a book and it's pure entertainment
yeah so now the um
uh Jo jolic thank you thank you Anthony
I appreciate
that and we should we're gon to get you
guys uh pretty quick here but um the
last question I have for you Jen is if
you had a magic
wand what would you do with it right now
you have one
wish what would you do with it h
M there's part of me that would
um uh like wish eternal life on my
family because as we are all getting
older we're realizing our parents are
getting older and that's a sad thing oh
my goodness like it's a very sad thing
uh part of me would also like to not
have all the money in the world but have
the capability to always be in the right
mindset and in the right place to be
thinking about how to make money MH and
um having the skills to be ahead of the
curve and uh make that money like so
it's it's it's all security for me if I
had a magic wand I would create security
for myself because I've learned in this
entrepreneur game I need a certain sense
of security and I think everybody has
their different thresholds of what that
means but like having my family in place
and having just not a I don't need tens
of thousands of dollars a month I need
to be able to make sure that this roof
stays over my head that's my sense of
security yeah I you know that is is
something that we all feel right some
people don't want to admit it but you
know you know I every day it doesn't
matter what how much money I get or
whatever whatever the situation I'm
always me going vegan though um I'm not
as a I'm not as anxious cuz before I was
really anxious I'm like oh shoot like I
didn't close someone by by the 15th of
the month and I have kind of like a rule
I have a twoe rule if you're not making
money in two weeks you're not going to
make money for the rest of the week or
the rest of the two weeks that's how I
look at it for the okay yeah so um
because bills come out on the 15th and
then if you can't you can't pay that
you're screwed so I always if I don't
make money by the 15th I always do but
like if I don't make money by the 15th
um I'm always panicking but eating vegan
I'm like you know I'm I'm kind of coast
I'm like yeah everything will be all
right but I think I still think about
always trying to do better and I always
want to make sure that things are secure
you know I'll buy like subscriptions for
a year because I just don't like the
idea of you know having to just monitor
things I always like to make sure that I
have everything in place so I hear you
on
that yeah there's a lot of things behind
the scenes in this journey that is
entrepreneurship that you have never
experienced about yourself I thought
Iraq was
hard
no no I mean I've seen some stuff and
you I've been prepared for it right my
military training the training that I
received when I was in the dod legit
prepared me for almost every scenario
that I went through there is like no
handbook there is no it's like having a
kid right there's when you have your
first kid there's no handbook for that
at all you figure it out along the way
well I think that's true for everybody's
like first business
and then any point that they want to um
push forward so any growth tracks or any
you know expansions there's really no
Playbook because it's an individual path
it's an individual journey and and you
just got to you got to be constantly
creative and and and bootstrap a
lot I don't know how to sugarcoat this
it's like it's ugly just like real
estate or car like I did um car sales
and stuff if you're going to do anything
where where you are your bread winner
you have to be prepared you gotta you
got to save your money you got to have
some sort of Nest Egg you got to have
that support or if you don't have the
money you have to have a support system
because my my mentors my sister you know
when I first started this business she
loan me a th000 bucks I mean I had to do
it because I was going to you know I
didn't want to lose my house and I have
a kid so lose my house and then lose my
kid in the same breath and I wasn't to
do that you know we you know you just
have to you have to fight but um let's
take a look at the comments because I
feel like I've been neglecting them I'm
sorry I couldn't give you guys all the
flash I realized that a lot of The Flash
is uh probably the reason why the
internet connection is going down oh so
you know what like there's some secrets
that that I use in my other broadcast I
didn't use for this one so I'm gonna
have to go back to you know square one
so that we that these uh broadcasts run
smooth but um you know I want to say hi
to all the people that are in so we have
Wilston a young we have Rob from from
Bishop mcdal Rob um Ed Edmund Stone we
have Peter Ernest we got uh Anthony we
got Shamar we got stutch one of my
clients thank you thank you Pierre Evans
so where all the comments did people
leave comments let me just refresh do
you see comments over there
yeah I see comments uh I saw Monica came
in I saw Brett he told you early on
about the some of the issues Dan Keller
said hello Chris Ripka came by which I
met on blab as well Anthony Davis was
the one who gave all the comments for
Mila Jo jovic jovic I am you know I'm
not that person that can pronounce names
eloquently me neither um but who was in
The Fifth Element and then stutch said
good stuff bro and then I see William
CIS has come by and Craig nessian who I
used to work with hi Greg and then
Tiffany Kaiser who's a friend of mine
who's over across the pond right now and
it is it is really late for you Tiffany
what are you doing up but thank you for
being here that's awesome so uh and then
Anthony Davis says now I know I hit Jen
Nelson with a chocolate pie yeah now he
now he wants to hit me with a chocolate
pie Anthony you're a
troublemaker oh and we got William in
the house so thank you guys all we got
to hustle own trivia right next after
this so um I'm gonna have to let you go
Jen but Jen wait but wait there's more
Ryan oh oh oh but
wait so do so I spent a little time on
the Mario Armstrong never settle show
and I've been holding this for a special
occasion we got a great swag bag and
there was one element in the swag bag
that I kind of was like I know who needs
this swag more than I do right um and
it's in this it's in this box it's in
this little box do you see the box it's
from America
apparently
called so you got to tell me you got to
tell
me get all excited about
it whoa how how many how many wooden how
many wooden bow ties do you have I have
two okay tell me what they look like
this looks like it looks both of them
look like this okay have any pattern on
them mine has a purple stripe
pattern okay how about how about that
one oh my
goodness holy moly I think this has got
your name all over it oh it does I'll
thank you so much wow this screams this
just screams you and I'm so glad so it's
old school craftsmanship modern style we
give from the two guys bowai Co and I as
soon as I saw it I'm like I only know
one guy that's going to really love this
and cherish it the way that it needs to
be so I'm going to send it to you Ryan
oh my goodness Jen I can't believe that
what it fits for you it's a perfect
match like you always want to give
something to somebody that it'll mean
something for them and I like your bow
ties I've always liked your bow ties so
I want to encourage that behavior from
you oh my goodness folks oh my goodness
I made Ryan oh my
goodness it's like I don't know like I'm
I'm a person that if you're going to
give a gift you know if you don't if
there's no meaning behind it don't give
it like that's how I am because I I
really appreciate the thought because no
one knows where these come from I don't
really tell nobody you know what I mean
but the uh they don't like I don't
really go around it but the fact that
you saw it and you know even to bring it
on the show I was like damn like even if
you were wow oh yeah I'll give you I
like gifts that are perfect I like gifts
that match and I don't like like I'm bad
at remembering birthdays and holidays
and stuff like that and getting it I'd
rather just have that moment and find
something perfect perfect and just give
it like that's that means so much more
to me wow I'm going to cry
now good you made me cry on air
almost well that's that's a good thing
then uh that means we're we're we that
means you gave your all and you know
you're being honest and I really
appreciate it this was uh besides the
technical difficulties like I couldn't
make any like changes or anything like
that on this broadcast today because I
didn't want anything to to mess up
because this was an like honest to God
it was a special occasion and now even
more special because I decided to put
that bow tie on so it you know this is
going to be one of those uh you know the
one of these one of the shows that I'm
going to be replaying you know and
showing people because it's it was a
special moment because you did really
encourage me to you know just to like I
have a problem with committing to things
and doing things like I always I live in
my head and I create and I and I'm like
oh I got add let me go on this next
project and I leave things behind but
you're the first person to really
recognize that you know the gift within
me and I should be consistent and you
know bring something forward so again
this is a special occasion thank you so
much folks vit mug check them out check
them out the link is in the chat I saw
um yeah I did I stuck that in
there um vit mug wine Antics and you
want to sign up for ladies go live the
virtual uh Summit it's a virtual Summit
this is the first that I've ever seen on
Facebook live um platform so um you
definitely want to check check them out
and uh Jen you're more than welcome to
come back on the show um even to be a
contact UM contributor and I could tell
you talk to you about that stuff online
or offline so thank you so much Jen for
for coming for before you go one one one
more tradition well wait there's
more so um I'm doing a U well actually
I'll explain to you afterwards but um I
do a call and response so when I say
welcome to the you scream hustle Zone as
loud as you possibly can okay no ex
sleeping there's people sleeping here
well we're gonna have to wake them up oh
shoot so into the
mic welcome to the the hustle
Zone that's what you get thank
you I like that hustle Zone that's what
you get that's what you get all right
thank you so much Jen folks we'll be
back um we are a little bit late but we
we'll be back for the hustle on trivia
with Monica she's going to be coming on
so I'm super excited about that uh and
this is the this is the first of many
hustles on TV um segment so you want to
tune in uh the other thing too is you
guys want to sign up to the hustle Zone
uh TV group um and to the and like the
page so that you guys can get the event
the event um not event requests what do
you call them event advertisements and
and you know with guest like Jen um you
definitely want to tune in um by liking
our page cuz all the exclusive content
will be there and don't forget to check
out our t-shirt line hustle zone. clo so
hustle zone. and you'll see some of our
Classic t-shirts and you should be
seeing soon our new our new line with
the new logo and whatnot um so thank you
guys all for tuning in and for
commenting make sure you share it one
more time just share put it on people's
page because they had to see this this
was an amazing interview Jen thank you
so much for for being a guest thank you
I appreciate it all right have a good
one talk to you guys in like 10
minutes okay bye hold on and my my mouse
is frozen and it's frozen